

ANIL **PANWAR**

PYTHON DEVELOPER

About Me

I am a highly motivated IT professional with over 14 years of experience in software development and project management. I possess excellent problem-solving skills and a strong commitment to delivering high-quality work. Seeking a challenging role in an IT company where I can utilize my skills and grow professionally.

公 Skills

Python



Django Framework



Rest API



AWS



HTML, CSS, JS, Ajax



Knowledge of Machine learning, Numpy, Pandas, Postman, Github, Selenium, Nginx server setup

Education

Master of Technology (IT)

IIPS, DAVV, Indore 2004 - 2009

Higher Secondary

SMVP, Indore 2002 - 2003



Work Experience

Python Experience - 9 Years Total Experience - 14 Years

2023-2024

Simplifi Dentistry Solutions India Pvt. Ltd.

March 2023 - Feb 2024 (11 months)

Senior Software Engineer

Project - Dentistry Automation

Role - To Scrape data from various websites. using python ,selenium

2022-2023

Silvergrey Technologies Pvt. Ltd. Aug-2022 - Feb-2023 (6 months) Project Manager

Project - Classic

Role - **Python** Full stack developer. Project developed by using python,django,javascript,ajax,html and css. link - http://107.155.116.144/

Project - American Screening, Role - API Developer. Project developed by using Django Rest Framework.

<u>2010-2022</u>

IES, IPS Academy, Indore 2010-2022 (12 Years)

Project - Campus Active Management System, Role - Full Stack Developer, Project Developed by using **Python, Django**, Html, Css. **(8 Years)**

Project - Leave Management System, Role - Backend Developer, Project Developed by using Php, Sql.

EurekaBike - 2018-2022 (4.4 years)

Freelancer - Python Developer

Role - Python developer, Scraped data from varies websites and store in excel/csv file. Tool Used like python, selenium, openpyxl, javascript to fetch data from websites like Gaint, Trek, Cannondale, Bianchi, KTM, Scott, Bergamount, BBF, Haibike, Cube.

Contact



14, Gopur colony, Indore, M.P. India



+919926081184



anilpanwar2031@gmail.com